A Guide to the Virginia Academy of Science Records, 1920-2005
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Box 43, James P. O'Brien Papers
  - Elizabeth River Project, 1994 (Box-folder 43-45)
  - VAS Campaign, May 1994 (Box-folder 43-46)
  - Fund Raising, 1994 (Box-folder 43-47)
  - VAS 75th Anniv. Committee, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 43-48)
  - VQUEST News, 1994 (Box-folder 43-49)
  - Memos, 1993 (Box-folder 43-50)